A Finding Aid to the Paul Jenkins Papers, circa 1915-2010, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Paul Jenkins papers
circa 1915-2010
Archives of American Art
Jenkins, Paul, 1923-2012
AAA.jenkpaul2
Archival Resource Key
11.1 Linear feet
The papers of abstract expressionist painter and playwright Paul Jenkins measure 11.1 linear feet and date from circa 1915 to 2010. Jenkins's career in New York and Paris is documented through biographical material, family papers, correspondence, writings, personal business records, printed material, photographs of Jenkins in his studio and at various events, and original artwork by Jenkins and others.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research. Access to original papers requires an appointment and is limited to the Archives' Washington, D.C. Research Center.
Related Materials
Also found at the Archives of American Art are an interview of Paul Jenkins, August 1969, conducted by Albert Elsen, and an oral history interview, 1968, conducted by Colette Roberts.
Biographical / Historical
Paul Jenkins (1923-2012) was an abstract expressionist painter and playwright in New York, New York, and Paris, France. Jenkins was born in Kansas City, Missouri in 1923, and moved to Youngstown, Ohio as a teenager. After serving in the U.S. Maritime Service and the U.S. Naval Air Corps, Jenkins studied playwriting with George McCalmon at the Carnegie Institute of Technology (now Carnegie Mellon University). In 1948, he moved to New York City, where he studied with Yasuo Kuniyoshi at the Art Students League of New York.
Over the course of his career, Jenkins experimented with multiple techniques, including oil on primed canvas, flowing paints, acrylics, watercolor, and mixed media collages. After traveling extensively and meeting many artists, Jenkins ultimately became associated with the Abstract Expressionists. His work gained the attention of other members of the art world and he held solo exhibitions at venues such as the Zoe Dusanne Gallery in Seattle and the Martha Jackson Gallery in New York. Jenkins' paintings were purchased by both museums and private collectors, including the Museum of Modern Art, the Whitney Museum of American Art, and Peggy Guggenheim.
In addition to his painting, Jenkins continued to explore other creative endeavors. He experimented with sculpture, producing works for events and permanent displays, including the Sculptors' Symposium at the Cooper-Hewitt Museum and the Sculpture Garden of the Hofstra Museum. His plays, such as Strike the Puma, were published and performed off Broadway in New York City. Jenkins's art served as the backdrop for multiple stage productions, and in 1978, his paintings were featured in the Academy Award nominated movie An Unmarried Woman. Jenkins also collaborated on a number of book projects, including Anatomy of a Cloud, a collection of autobiographical collages and texts.
Throughout his adult life, Jenkins split most of his time between New York and Paris. He continued to create and exhibit new works until his death in New York in 2012.
Scope and Contents
The papers of abstract expressionist painter and playwright Paul Jenkins measure 11.1 linear feet and date from circa 1915 to 2010. Jenkins's career in New York and Paris is documented through biographical material, family papers, correspondence, writings, personal business records, printed material, photographs of Jenkins in his studio and at various events, and original artwork by Jenkins and others.
Biographical material and family papers consist of awards and certificates, calendars, marriage, divorce, and estate papers, and military service records. Also included are family papers and a scrapbook belonging to Jenkins's aunt, Louise Jenkins.
Correspondence, which makes up the bulk of the collection, is with family, friends, and fellow artists, including Alice Baber, Norman Bluhm, Willem de Kooning, and Lee Krasner Pollock, as well as art organizations, schools, museums, galleries, and gallery owners, such as the Art Students League of New York, New York University, Museum of Modern Art, Martha Jackson Gallery, Zoe Dusanne, and Peggy Guggenheim.
Writings includes scattered writings by Paul Jenkins, two of his travel diaries, and the guest book for an exhibition in Tokyo. Also found are a copy of Lili Krahmer Verame's China travel diary and the writings and research materials of others.
Personal business records consist of financial records, lease documents, price lists, travel documents, and papers regarding Jenkins's rental property. Also included are a file on the New York University medal designed by Jenkins and a file concerning a Karl Prantl statue.
Printed material consists of event programs, newsletters, bulletins, member reports, press releases, art exhibition announcements and catalogs, concert and theater announcements and programs, news and magazine clippings, and obituaries and memorial announcements.
Artwork contains miscellaneous sketches and collages by Paul Jenkins. Additional artworks include sketches, watercolors, and prints by other artists, as well as 8 oversize mixed media sketches by Frank Prince of Jenkins's Meditation Mandala Sundial sculptures.
Photographs of Paul Jenkins depict him in his studio, with family and friends, and at events. Photographs of family and friends include Esther Ebenhoe Jenkins, Alice Baber Jenkins, Norman Bluhm, Thomas Erma, Françoise Gilot, Matsumi "Mike," Carole, and Bunshi Paul Kanemitsu, and Frank Prince.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 7 series:
Missing Title
Series 1: Biographical Material, circa 1915-1997 (Box 1; 9 folders)
Series 2: Correspondence, circa 1930-2010 (Box 1-9, 13; 9 linear feet)
Series 3: Writings, circa 1950-2003 (Box 9-10; 0.5 linear feet)
Series 4: Personal Business Records, circa 1944-1990 (Box 10; 0.3 linear feet)
Series 5: Printed Material, circa 1952-2010 (Box 10-11; 0.6 linear feet)
Aeries 6: Artwork, circa 1935-2007 (Box 11-12, OV 14; 0.2 linear feet)
Series 7: Photography, circa 1940-1998 (Box 12; 0.4 linear feet)
Provenance
The papers were donated 2007-2009 and in 2012 by Paul and Suzanne Jenkins.
Travel diaries; Abstract expressionism; Manuscripts; Sketches; Watercolors; Artists' studios -- Photographs; China -- Description and Travel; Prints; Dramatists -- France -- Paris; Collages; Visitors' books; Medals -- Design; Painters -- France -- Paris; Painters -- New York (State) -- New York; Photographs; Scrapbooks; Dramatists -- New York (State) -- New York; De Kooning, Willem, 1904-1997; Jenkins, Esther Ebenhoe; Bluhm, Norman, 1921-1999; Krasner, Lee, 1908-1984; Baber, Alice; Erma, Thomas, 1939-1964; Prantl, Karl; Dusanne, Zoe, -1977; Prince, Frank; Art Students League (New York, N.Y.); New York University; Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.); Guggenheim, Peggy, 1898-1979; Gilot, Francoise, 1921-; Martha Jackson Gallery
- Biographical Material and Family Papers, circa 1915-1997; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 0.1 Linear feet Box 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains biographical material documenting Jenkins's life and career, including awards and certificates, calendars, marriage, divorce, and estate papers, and military service records. Also found are family papers and a scrapbook belonging to Jenkins's aunt, Louise Jenkins.
  - Awards and Certificates, 1975-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Calendars, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Divorce Papers, 1962-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Estate Papers, 1947-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Family Papers, Esther Ebenhoe Jenkins, 1944-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Family Papers, Miscellaneous, circa 1917-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marriage Papers, 1945-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Military Service Papers, 1945-1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook, Louise Jenkins, circa 1915-1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, circa 1930-2010; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 9 Linear feet Box 1-9, Box 13
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by last name, with sent and recieved correspondence filed together. Persons with three or fewer items of correspondence are filed in the miscellaneous folders, which are also arranged alphabetically.
  Correspondence is with family, friends, fellow artists, art organizations, schools, museums, galleries, and gallery owners. Also found are copies of Jenkins's outgoing correspondence.
  Of note is correspondence with friends and fellow artists, including Alice Baber, Norman Bluhm, Willem de Kooning, and Lee Krasner Pollock, as well as art organizations, schools, museums, galleries, and gallery owners, such as the Art Students League of New York, New York University, Museum of Modern Art, Martha Jackson Gallery, Zoe Dusanne, and Peggy Guggenheim.
  - Abrams, Harry and Nina, circa 1964-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Actors Studio, 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adelmann Olsen, Marianne, circa 1964-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adler, Richard, 1970-1981, 2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alley, Anthea, circa 1960-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alloway, Lawrence, circa 1953-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Anderson, Harry W. "Hunk", 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Andrews, Stephen, circa 1985-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arman, Armand "Arman" and Corice, circa 2004-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Armengard, Françoise, 1987-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arroyo, Eduardo, 1983-1983, 1995-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Art Students League of New York, 1969-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Ashton, Dore, circa 1955-1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Aurbach, Jerry and Craig, Charles, circa 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Aurbach, Jerry and Craig, Charles, circa 1982-1994, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - A, Miscellaneous: Aa-Alp, circa 1956-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Scope and Contents note
    (Includes Anouk Aimée)
  - A, Miscellaneous: Alq-An, circa 1963-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A, Miscellaneous: Aq-Av, circa 1965-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
    (Includes Jean Attali)
  - Baber, Adin, circa 1963-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Baber Jenkins, Alice, circa 1960-1966, 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Barash, Jeffrey, 1999-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Barber, Peter, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Barker, John, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Barrault, Jean-Louis and Renaud, Madeline, circa 1966-1986, 1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bates, Alan and Benedick, circa 1977-1978, 2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Bates, Martin, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Bavoillot, Gisou, circa 1981-1983, 2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bazelon, Cecile and Irwin "Buddy", circa 1962-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Benmussa, Simone, circa 1982-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Berkson, Muriel, circa 1965-1966, 1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Biddle, Flora (Miller), 1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Binh, Le Nhât, circa 1992-1998, 2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Bishop, Thomas and Helen, 1976-1985, 2008-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Bluhm, Norman, circa 1950-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 43-44)
  - Bluhm, Norman, circa 1960-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Bocour, Leonard, 1974-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Bonafoux, Pascal, 1983-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Bosquet, Alain, 1976-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Bowen, Denis and Judy, circa 1963, 1989-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Braun-Monk, Eugene, circa 1991-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Bray, Barbara, 1973-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Briet, Philippe, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Bruyère, André and Boba, circa 1980-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Bryan, Sheldon and Carol, circa 1962-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Burns, Edward, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Bursztynowicz, Henry, 1984-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Ba, circa 1956-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 57)
    (Includes Will Barnet)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Be-Berl, circa 1962-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bern-Bi, circa 1945-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 59)
    (Includes Pierre Bernard, Edward Betts)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Bl-Bo, circa 1965-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 60)
    (Includes François Boisrond, Stanley Boxer)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Br-Brul, circa 1962-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 61)
    (Includes Paul Brach)
  - B, Miscellaneous: Brun-Bu, circa 1969-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Carter, Clarence and Mary, circa 1966-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cartwright, Carroll L. and Connie, 1991-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cato, Robert "Bob", circa 1966-1987, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Charles, Rollo, National Museum of Wales, Cardiff, 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Christo and Jeanne-Claude, 2000-2009; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Clergue, Lucien and Yolande, circa 1981-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cochrane, Cara, circa 1963-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cochrane, Gavin, circa 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cochrane, J. Peter "J.P.W.", circa 1956-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cochrane, J. Peter "J.P.W.", 1980-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cochrane, J. Peter "J.P.W.", 1998-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cochrane, Patricia, circa 1960-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cornette De Saint-Cyr, Pierre, 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cummings, Paul, 1964-1968, 1983-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Ca-Cha, circa 1954-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    (Includes Alice Cahana, Lawrence "Larry" Calcagno, Joseph and Jean (Erdman) Campbell, Truman Capote, Walter Chappell)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Che-Ci, circa 1960-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    (Includes Oscar Chelimsky)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Cl-Com, circa 1955-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    (Includes William Clift)
  - C, Miscellaneous: Con-Cu, circa 1943-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    (Includes Philip C. Curtis)
  - De Carmel, Anna, circa 1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - De Givenchy, Hubert, 1973-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - De Kooning, Willem "Bill" and Elaine, 1963-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Delaney, Beauford, circa 1953-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - De Rothschild, Alix, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - De Villandry, François, circa 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Dobkin, John and Immaculada, 1983-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Duhl, Leonard J., circa 1973-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dubuffet, Jean, 1954-1961, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Duncan, David Douglas and Sheila, circa 1964-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Duncan, David Douglas and Sheila, circa 1967-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Duncan, David Douglas and Sheila, circa 1978-1996, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, 1935-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, 1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, 1955-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, circa 1956-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Dusanne, Zoe, Correspondence from Others, circa 1955-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Dusanne, Zoe from Paul Jenkins, circa 1955-1963, 2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Dusanne Young, Theodosia, 1978-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Dutilleux, Henri, 1990-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Da-Dek, circa 1964-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 42)
    (Includes Alan and Bili Davie, Avel De Knight)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Del-Don, circa 1962-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 43)
    (Includes Pierre Demarne, Enrico Donati)
  - D, Miscellaneous: Dor-Du, circa 1954-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Eastman, Lee V. and Monique, circa 1977-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Eban, Aubrey "Abba" and Suzy, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Ebenhoch, Sara, 1945-1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 48-50)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4-9)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, 1953-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, circa 1957-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther, circa 1963-1970, 1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, circa 1943-1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17-20)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, circa 1944-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22-26)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1948-1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - Ebenhoe Jenkins, Esther from Paul Jenkins, 1958-1959, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Eckaus, Risha, circa 1963-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Elliot, George P. and Mary Emma, 1960-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia, circa 1962-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia, circa 1974-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia from Paul Jenkins, 1963-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia from Paul Jenkins, circa 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Elsen, Albert E. and Patricia from Paul Jenkins, 1982-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Elsen, Sharon, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Emmerich, André, 1958-1963, 1974-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Erdman, Jean, 1975-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Erma, Thomas, circa 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - E, Miscellaneous, circa 1964-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Facchetti, Paul and Jeanne, 1957-1959, 1986, 2001-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    (Includes Paul Emsley, John Entenza)
  - Falkenstein, Claire, circa 1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Faucher, Michel, circa 1986-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fellers, Iona, 1966-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fellers-Spencer, Beulah, 1968-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fils, Melita, circa 1953-1956; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fink, Don and Yvonne, 1964-1967, 1978, 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fitzsimmons, James, 1954-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Fordyce, Alice and Al, circa 1964-1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Forrester, John and Ann, circa 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Forrester, John and Ann, circa 1954-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Frame-Thomson, Enid, circa 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Francis, Muriel Goodwin and Sam, 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Franck, Klaus, 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Francken, Ruth, circa 1957-1966, 1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Friedlander, Ira and Barbara, circa 1969-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Friedman, B.H. "Bob" and Abby, circa 1981-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fa-Fe, circa 1966-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    (Includes Jean Fanchette, Paul Feiler)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fi-Ford, circa 1961-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Fordy-Franc, circa 1954-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    (Includes Milton S. Fox)
  - F, Miscellaneous: Frank-Fu, circa 1972-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
    (Includes Sideo Fromboluti)
  - Gadaud, André and Monique, 1980-1995, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Garelli, Claude and Jaques, 1981, 2004-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Garniez, Bernard, 1980-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Gary, Helen, 1965-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Gastineau, Joséphine, Galerie d'Art Moderne, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Gattegno, Alberto, 1971-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Gervis, Daniel, 1967-1968, 2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Getz, Ilse and Danes, Gibson, circa 1963-1966, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Gill, Robert, 1945-1954, 1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Gilot, Françoise, circa 1966-1980, 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Gimpel, Gudrun and Kay, 1978, 1988-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Glimcher, Mildred "Milly", 1963, 1994-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Goldberg, Michael, circa 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Golden, Mark and Barbara, circa 1985-1987, 2005-2008; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Gonthier, Jean-François, 1965-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Götz, K.O., 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Grant, Winona, 1956-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Greenberg, Clement and Jenny, 1956-1974, 1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Greis, Otto and Hannelore, 1954-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 56)